Guide to the Cass Gilbert Papers and Architectural Drawings 1883-1952 (Bulk 1900-1934) PR 21
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Project Files
  - Subseries I: Foldered Material
    - Hotel on C&O Railroad (Lexington, KY), 1904 (Offsite-box 126)
    - Hudson River Bridge (Hudson River, NY) (Box 1 of 5), 1925-1933 (Offsite-box 126)
    - Hudson River Bridge (Hudson River, NY) (Box 2 of 5), 1925-1933 (Offsite-box 127)
    - Hudson River Bridge (Hudson River, NY) (Box 3 of 5), 1925-1933 (Offsite-box 128)
    - Hudson River Bridge (Hudson River, NY) (Box 4 of 5), 1925-1933 (Offsite-box 129)
    - Hudson River Bridge (Hudson River, NY) (Box 5 of 5), 1925-1933 (Offsite-box 130)
    - Illuminating Engineering Company, 1904 (Offsite-box 130)
    - Interzone Building (New York, NY) (Box 1 of 5), 1920-1934 (Offsite-box 130)
    - Interzone Building (New York, NY) (Box 2 of 5), 1920-1934 (Offsite-box 131)
    - Interzone Building (New York, NY) (Box 3 of 5), 1920-1934 (Offsite-box 132)
    - Interzone Building (New York, NY) (Box 4 of 5), 1920-1934 (Offsite-box 133)
    - Interzone Building (New York, NY) (Box 5 of 5), 1920-1934 (Offsite-box 134)
    - Ives Memorial Library (New Haven, CT) (Box 1 of 6), 1907-1932 (Offsite-box 134)
    - Ives Memorial Library (New Haven, CT) (Box 2 of 6), 1907-1932 (Offsite-box 135)
    - Ives Memorial Library (New Haven, CT) (Box 3 of 6), 1907-1932 (Offsite-box 136)
    - Ives Memorial Library (New Haven, CT) (Box 4 of 6), 1907-1932 (Offsite-box 137)
    - Ives Memorial Library (New Haven, CT) (Box 5 of 6), 1907-1932 (Offsite-box 138)
    - Ives Memorial Library (New Haven, CT) (Box 6 of 6), 1907-1932 (Offsite-box 139)
    - Jamaica Estates (Long Island, NY) (Box 1 of 2), 1908-1911 (Offsite-box 139)
    - Jamaica Estates (Long Island, NY) (Box 2 of 2), 1908-1911 (Offsite-box 140)
    - James House (Greenwich, CT), 1931-1932 (Offsite-box 140)
    - Johnson Cement Coating, 1900-1901 (Offsite-box 140)
    - Kill Van Kull Bridge (Bayonne, NJ), 1926-1931 (Offsite-box 140)
    - Kinney Building (Newark, NJ) (Box 1 of 10), 1912-1930 (Offsite-box 140)
    - Kinney Building (Newark, NJ) (Box 2 of 10), 1912-1930 (Offsite-box 141)
    - Kinney Building (Newark, NJ) (Box 3 of 10), 1912-1930 (Offsite-box 142)
    - Kinney Building (Newark, NJ) (Box 4 of 10), 1912-1930 (Offsite-box 143)
    - Kinney Building (Newark, NJ) (Box 5 of 10), 1912-1930 (Offsite-box 144)
    - Kinney Building (Newark, NJ) (Box 6 of 10), 1912-1930 (Offsite-box 145)
    - Kinney Building (Newark, NJ) (Box 7 of 10), 1912-1930 (Offsite-box 146)
    - Kinney Building (Newark, NJ) (Box 8 of 10), 1912-1930 (Offsite-box 147)
    - Kinney Building (Newark, NJ) (Box 9 of 10), 1912-1930 (Offsite-box 148)
    - Kinney Building (Newark, NJ) (Box 10 of 10), 1912-1930 (Offsite-box 149)
    - Le Clere, Francis, 1901 (Offsite-box 149)
    - Lincoln House (Waterbury, CT), 1916-1918 (Offsite-box 149)
    - Loney Tomb (Skaneateles, NY), 1900-1910 (Offsite-box 150)
    - Losey Memorial (La Crosse, WI), 1901 (Offsite-box 150)
    - Louisiana Purchase Exposition (later the St. Louis Art Museum) (Box 1 of 5), 1901-1919 (Offsite-box 150)
    - Louisiana Purchase Exposition (later the St. Louis Art Museum) (Box 2 of 5), 1901-1919 (Offsite-box 151)
    - Louisiana Purchase Exposition (later the St. Louis Art Museum) (Box 3 of 5), 1901-1919 (Offsite-box 152)
    - Louisiana Purchase Exposition (later the St. Louis Art Museum) (Box 4 of 5), 1901-1919 (Offsite-box 153)
    - Louisiana Purchase Exposition (later the St. Louis Art Museum) (Box 5 of 5), 1901-1919 (Offsite-box 154)
    - Lyon Cottage (White Bear Lake, MN), Undated (Offsite-box 154)
    - Macey Office Furniture, 1901 (Offsite-box 154)
    - Madison High School (Madison, WI) (Box 1 of 4), 1903-1909 (Offsite-box 154)
    - Madison High School (Madison, WI) (Box 2 of 4), 1903-1909 (Offsite-box 155)
    - Madison High School (Madison, WI) (Box 3 of 4), 1903-1909 (Offsite-box 156)
    - Madison High School (Madison, WI) (Box 4 of 4), 1903-1909 (Offsite-box 157)
    - Manhattan Press Clippings Bureau, 1901 (Offsite-box 157)
    - Mannheimer Memorial Fountain (St. Paul, MN), 1904-1906 (Offsite-box 157)
    - Marble Companies, 1901, 1905 (Offsite-box 157)
    - McKinley National Memorial (Canton, OH), 1904-1905 (Offsite-box 157)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 1 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 158)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 2 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 159)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 3 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 160)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 4 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 161)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 5 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 162)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 6 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 163)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 7 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 164)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 8 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 165)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 9 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 166)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 10 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 167)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 11 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 168)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 12 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 169)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 13 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 170)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 14 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 171)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 15 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 172)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 16 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 173)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 17 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 174)
    - Minnesota State Capital (St. Paul, MN) (Box 18 of 18), 1901-1933 (Offsite-box 175)
    - Montana Club (Helena, MT) (Box 1 of 2), 1903-1913 (Offsite-box 175)
    - Montana Club (Helena, MT) (Box 2 of 2), 1903-1913 (Offsite-box 176)
    - Montana State University (Missoula and Bozeman, MT), 1916-1919 (Offsite-box 176)
    - Montana State Capitol (Butte, MT), undated (Offsite-box 176)
    - Monuments- First Division Memorial Association, 1922-1923 (Offsite-box 176)
    - Monuments- Jusserand Memorial (Washington, DC), 1932-1934 (Offsite-box 176)
    - Monuments- C.S. Pietro (Paris, France), 1917 (Offsite-box 176)
    - Monuments-Monument to the Preservation of Knowledge, 1933 (Offsite-box 176)
    - Monuments- Tennessee Memorial Competition (Nashville, TN), 1921-1922 (Offsite-box 176)
    - Mt. Vernon Shelter (Mt. Vernon, NY), 1922 (Offsite-box 177)
    - National State Savings Bank (Newark, NJ) (Box 1 of 4), 1909-1921 (Offsite-box 178)
    - National State Savings Bank (Newark, NJ) (Box 2 of 4), 1909-1921 (Offsite-box 179)
    - National State Savings Bank (Newark, NJ) (Box 3 of 4), 1909-1921 (Offsite-box 180)
    - National State Savings Bank (Newark, NJ) (Box 4 of 4), 1909-1921 (Offsite-box 181)
    - New Business (Box 1 of 13), 1899-1935 (Offsite-box 181)
    - New Business (Box 2 of 13), 1899-1935 (Offsite-box 182)
    - New Business (Box 3 of 13), 1899-1935 (Offsite-box 183)
    - New Business (Box 4 of 13), 1899-1935 (Offsite-box 184)
    - New Business (Box 5 of 13), 1899-1935 (Offsite-box 185)
    - New Business (Box 6 of 13), 1899-1935 (Offsite-box 186)
    - New Business (Box 7 of 13), 1899-1935 (Offsite-box 187)
    - New Business (Box 8 of 13), 1899-1935 (Offsite-box 188)
    - New Business (Box 9 of 13), 1899-1935 (Offsite-box 189)
    - New Business (Box 10 of 13), 1899-1935 (Offsite-box 190)
    - New Business (Box 11 of 13), 1899-1935 (Offsite-box 191)
    - New Business (Box 12 of 13), 1899-1935 (Offsite-box 192)
    - New Business (Box 13 of 13), 1899-1935 (Offsite-box 193)
    - New York County Lawyer's Association (New York, NY) (Box 1 of 4), 1927-1934 (Offsite-box 193)
    - New York County Lawyer's Association (New York, NY) (Box 2 of 4), 1927-1934 (Offsite-box 194)
    - New York County Lawyer's Association (New York, NY) (Box 3 of 4), 1927-1934 (Offsite-box 195)
    - New York County Lawyer's Association (New York, NY) (Box 4 of 4), 1927-1934 (Offsite-box 196)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 1 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 196)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 2 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 197)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 3 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 198)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 4 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 199)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 5 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 200)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 6 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 201)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 7 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 202)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 8 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 203)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 9 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 204)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 10 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 205)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 11 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 206)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 12 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 207)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 13 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 208)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 14 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 209)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 15 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 210)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 16 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 211)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 17 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 212)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 18 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 213)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 19 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 214)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 20 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 215)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 21 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 216)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 22 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 217)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 23 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 218)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 24 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 219)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 25 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 220)
    - New York Life Insurance Building (New York, NY) (Box 26 of 26), 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 221)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- Bartow Station, NY (Box 1 of 2), 1907-1911 (Offsite-box 221)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- Bartow Station, NY (Box 2 of 2), 1907-1911 (Offsite-box 222)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- Baychester Station, NY, 1907 (Offsite-box 222)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- Casanova Station, NY, 1907 (Offsite-box 222)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- Hunt's Point Station, NY, 1907-1909 (Offsite-box 223)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- Morris Park Station, NY (Box 1 of 2), 1907-1911 (Offsite-box 223)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- Morris Park Station, NY (Box 2 of 2), 1907-1911 (Offsite-box 224)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- New Haven Station, CT (Box 1 of 8), 1906-1923 (Offsite-box 224)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- New Haven Station, CT (Box 2 of 8), 1906-1923 (Offsite-box 225)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- New Haven Station, CT (Box 3 of 8), 1906-1923 (Offsite-box 226)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- New Haven Station, CT (Box 4 of 8), 1906-1923 (Offsite-box 227)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- New Haven Station, CT (Box 5 of 8), 1906-1923 (Offsite-box 228)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- New Haven Station, CT (Box 6 of 8), 1906-1923 (Offsite-box 229)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- New Haven Station, CT (Box 7 of 8), 1906-1923 (Offsite-box 230)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- New Haven Station, CT (Box 8 of 8), 1906-1923 (Offsite-box 231)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- Pelham Manor Station, NY (Box 1 of 2), 1907-1909 (Offsite-box 231)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- Pelham Manor Station, NY (Box 2 of 2), 1907-1909 (Offsite-box 232)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- Port Morris Station, NY (Box 1 of 2), 1907-1911 (Offsite-box 232)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- Port Morris Station, NY (Box 2 of 2), 1907-1911 (Offsite-box 233)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- Van Nest Station, NY, 1908 (Offsite-box 233)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- West Farms Station, NY, 1907 (Offsite-box 233)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Stations- Westchester Avenue Station, NY, 1907-1911 (Offsite-box 233)
    - Niagara Frontier Bridge (became Grand Island Bridge) (Niagara Falls, NY), 1929-1932 (Offsite-box 234)
    - Norfolk Savings Bank and Trust Co. (Norfolk, VA), Undated (Offsite-box 234)
    - Northwestern National Bank (Minneapolis, MN), 1919-1931 (Offsite-box 234)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 1 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 235)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 2 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 236)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 3 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 237)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 4 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 238)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 5 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 239)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 6 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 240)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 7 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 241)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 8 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 242)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 9 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 243)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 10 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 244)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 11 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 245)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 12 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 246)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 13 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 247)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 14 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 248)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 15 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 249)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 16 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 250)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 17 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 251)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 18 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 252)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 19 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 253)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 20 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 254)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 21 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 255)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 22 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 256)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 23 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 257)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 24 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 258)
    - Oberlin College (Oberlin, OH) (Box 25 of 25), 1904-1934 (Offsite-box 259)
    - 130 West 30th Street (New York, NY) (Box 1 of 2), 1927-1930 (Offsite-box 259)
    - 130 West 30th Street (New York, NY) (Box 2 of 2), 1927-1930 (Offsite-box 260)
    - Pan American Exposition (Buffalo, NY), 1901 (Offsite-box 260)
    - Peixollo, Flonair, 1901 (Offsite-box 260)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 1 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 260)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 2 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 261)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 3 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 262)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 4 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 263)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 5 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 264)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 6 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 265)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 7 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 266)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 8 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 267)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 9 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 268)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 10 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 269)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 11 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 270)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 12 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 271)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 13 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 272)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 14 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 273)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 15 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 274)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 16 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 275)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 17 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 276)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 18 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 277)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 19 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 278)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 20 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 279)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Company Bridges and Buildings (Newark, NJ) (Box 21 of 21), 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 280)
    - Read, George R., 1901-1902 (Offsite-box 280)
    - Realty Company Warehouse (Great Falls, MT), 1901-1905 (Offsite-box 280)
    - Realty Company Warehouse (Minneapolis, MN), 1899-1910 (Offsite-box 280)
    - Red Wing Auditorium (Red Wing, MN), 1902 (Offsite-box 281)
    - Ridgefield Fountain (Ridgefield, CT), 1914-1916 (Offsite-box 281)
    - Rodin Studios (New York, NY) (Box 1 of 6), 1916-1918 (Offsite-box 281)
    - Rodin Studios (New York, NY) (Box 2 of 6), 1916-1918 (Offsite-box 282)
    - Rodin Studios (New York, NY) (Box 3 of 6), 1916-1918 (Offsite-box 283)
    - Rodin Studios (New York, NY) (Box 4 of 6), 1916-1918 (Offsite-box 284)
    - Rodin Studios (New York, NY) (Box 5 of 6), 1916-1918 (Offsite-box 285)
    - Rodin Studios (New York, NY) (Box 6 of 6), 1916-1918 (Offsite-box 286)
    - Romeike, Henry, 1901-1905 (Offsite-box 286)
    - Roselawn Cemetery (Rose Town, MN), 1902-1904 (Offsite-box 286)
    - Sailor's Snug Harbor Apartments (New York, NY), 1922 (Offsite-box 286)
    - Saint John the Divine Episcopal Church (Moorhead, MN), Undated (Offsite-box 286)
    - Saint John's the Evangelist (St.Paul, MN), 1901-1902 (Offsite-box 286)
    - Saint Louis Art Museum (see Louisiana Purchase Exposition) (Box X-ref)
    - Saint Louis First National Bank (St. Louis, MO), 1919-1921 (Offsite-box 287)
    - Saint Louis Hotel (Duluth, MN) (Box 1 of 3), 1901-1919 (Offsite-box 287)
    - Saint Louis Hotel (Duluth, MN) (Box 2 of 3), 1901-1919 (Offsite-box 288)
    - Saint Louis Hotel (Duluth, MN) (Box 3 of 3), 1901-1919 (Offsite-box 289)
    - Saint Louis Public Library (St. Louis, MO) (Box 1 of 15), 1907-1921 (Offsite-box 289)
    - Saint Louis Public Library (St. Louis, MO) (Box 2 of 15), 1907-1921 (Offsite-box 290)
    - Saint Louis Public Library (St. Louis, MO) (Box 3 of 15), 1907-1921 (Offsite-box 291)
    - Saint Louis Public Library (St. Louis, MO) (Box 4 of 15), 1907-1921 (Offsite-box 292)
    - Saint Louis Public Library (St. Louis, MO) (Box 5 of 15), 1907-1921 (Offsite-box 293)
    - Saint Louis Public Library (St. Louis, MO) (Box 6 of 15), 1907-1921 (Offsite-box 294)
    - Saint Louis Public Library (St. Louis, MO) (Box 7 of 15), 1907-1921 (Offsite-box 295)
    - Saint Louis Public Library (St. Louis, MO) (Box 8 of 15), 1907-1921 (Offsite-box 296)
    - Saint Louis Public Library (St. Louis, MO) (Box 9 of 15), 1907-1921 (Offsite-box 297)
    - Saint Louis Public Library (St. Louis, MO) (Box 10 of 15), 1907-1921 (Offsite-box 298)
    - Saint Louis Public Library (St. Louis, MO) (Box 11 of 15), 1907-1921 (Offsite-box 299)
    - Saint Louis Public Library (St. Louis, MO) (Box 12 of 15), 1907-1921 (Offsite-box 300)
    - Saint Louis Public Library (St. Louis, MO) (Box 13 of 15), 1907-1921 (Offsite-box 301)
    - Saint Louis Public Library (St. Louis, MO) (Box 14 of 15), 1907-1921 (Offsite-box 302)
    - Saint Louis Public Library (St. Louis, MO) (Box 15 of 15), 1907-1921 (Offsite-box 303)
    - Saint Peter's Hospital (Helena, MT), 1908-1912 (Offsite-box 303)
    - Scheuer Building (Newark, NJ) (Box 1 of 3), 1904-1917 (Offsite-box 304)
    - Scheuer Building (Newark, NJ) (Box 2 of 3), 1904-1917 (Offsite-box 305)
    - Scheuer Building (Newark, NJ) (Box 3 of 3), 1904-1917 (Offsite-box 306)
    - Schiller Monument (St. Paul, MN), 1905-1906 (Offsite-box 306)
    - School of Industrial Arts (Trenton, NJ) (Box 1 of 3), 1909-1931 (Offsite-box 306)
    - School of Industrial Arts (Trenton, NJ) (Box 2 of 3), 1909-1931 (Offsite-box 307)
    - School of Industrial Arts (Trenton, NJ) (Box 3 of 3), 1909-1931 (Offsite-box 308)
    - Scott Fountain and Belle Isle Bridge (Detroit, MI) (Box 1 of 7), 1914-1932 (Offsite-box 308)
    - Scott Fountain and Belle Isle Bridge (Detroit, MI) (Box 2 of 7), 1914-1932 (Offsite-box 309)
    - Scott Fountain and Belle Isle Bridge (Detroit, MI) (Box 3 of 7), 1914-1932 (Offsite-box 310)
    - Scott Fountain and Belle Isle Bridge (Detroit, MI) (Box 4 of 7), 1914-1932 (Offsite-box 311)
    - Scott Fountain and Belle Isle Bridge (Detroit, MI) (Box 5 of 7), 1914-1932 (Offsite-box 312)
    - Scott Fountain and Belle Isle Bridge (Detroit, MI) (Box 6 of 7), 1914-1932 (Offsite-box 313)
    - Scott Fountain and Belle Isle Bridge (Detroit, MI) (Box 7 of 7), 1914-1932 (Offsite-box 314)
    - Scoville Manufacturing Company (Waterbury, CT) (Box 1 of 2), 1917-1924 (Offsite-box 314)
    - Scoville Manufacturing Company (Waterbury, CT) (Box 2 of 2), 1917-1924 (Offsite-box 315)
    - Sculptors' Letters, 1901-1905 (Offsite-box 315)
    - Seaside Sanatorium (Waterford, CT) (Box 1 of 9), 1930-1934 (Offsite-box 315)
    - Seaside Sanatorium (Waterford, CT) (Box 2 of 9), 1930-1934 (Offsite-box 316)
    - Seaside Sanatorium (Waterford, CT) (Box 3 of 9), 1930-1934 (Offsite-box 317)
    - Seaside Sanatorium (Waterford, CT) (Box 4 of 9), 1930-1934 (Offsite-box 318)
    - Seaside Sanatorium (Waterford, CT) (Box 5 of 9), 1930-1934 (Offsite-box 319)
    - Seaside Sanatorium (Waterford, CT) (Box 6 of 9), 1930-1934 (Offsite-box 320)
    - Seaside Sanatorium (Waterford, CT) (Box 7 of 9), 1930-1934 (Offsite-box 321)
    - Seaside Sanatorium (Waterford, CT) (Box 8 of 9), 1930-1934 (Offsite-box 322)
    - Seaside Sanatorium (Waterford, CT) (Box 9 of 9), 1930-1934 (Offsite-box 323)
    - Second Church of Christ Scientist (Milwaukee, WI), 1903 (Offsite-box 323)
    - Seligman & Meyer, 1901-1903 (Offsite-box 323)
    - Shattuck School (Faribault, MN) (Box 1 of 2), 1901-1922 (Offsite-box 323)